当我告诉父亲我害怕躲在衣柜里的东西时
When I told dad I was scared of the thing in my closet,
他直接给了我一把四五式手枪
He gave me a.45.
那他应该怎么做
What was he supposed to do?
我当时才9岁
I was 9 years old.
是学习使用武器以及溶银做子弹的年龄吗
The weapon training and melting the silver into bullets?
老哥 迪恩 我们是被当作战士养大的
Man, dean, we were raised like warriors.
关紧门窗 拉上窗帘
Lock the doors and windows, close the shades.
最重要的是
And most important …
照看好萨姆
Watch out for sammy.
我无法理解你对他的言听计从
I don't understand the blind faith you have in the man.
这就是一个好儿子该做的
It's called being a good son.
爸爸会回来的 对吗
Dad's gonna be here, right?
他一定会回来的 我保证
He'll be here. promise.
- 他究竟去哪儿了 - 出差
- Where is he, anyway? - on business.
- 这就是你离家不归的原因 - 我只是去上大学
- And that's why you ran away. - I was just going to college.
是爸爸说走了就别再回来
It was dad who said if I was gonna go, I should stay gone.
你哥哥和我 我们都需要你
Your brother and me … we needed you.
你离我们而去 萨姆
You walked away, sam.
- 是你丢下了我们 - 都住口 你们俩
- You walked away! - stop it, both of you.
是你让我别再回来的 爸爸
You're the one who said, "don't come back, " dad.
你才是那个关上门的人 不是我
You're the one who closed that door, not me!
这绝不是我希望你拥有的生活
This is never the life that I wanted for you.
听着 我相信如果可能 爸爸一定会回来
Look, I'm sure dad would have been here if he could.
她真是个荡妇
She's such a slut.
怎样
So?
个人而言 我非常欣赏荡妇
Personally, I'm very pro-slut.
究竟发生了什么
What happened, anyway?
她可是让杰米·贾菲好好地受了次打击
She totally banged Jamie Jaffe, that's what.
完全颠覆了他心目中女牛仔形象
She gave him the reverse cowgirl and everything.
泰勒 你周末过得如何
Hi, Taylor. how was your weekend?
我认为还不错
Fine, I guess.
你没 没去参加牛仔竞技表演吗
You didn't… go to the rodeo?
那是我的位子
That's my spot.
抱歉 这里是淑女地带
Sorry. this is a skeev-free zone.
荡妇
Slut!
荡妇 荡妇
Slut! slut!
你根本不必在意那些混蛋们
You shouldn't listen to those jerks.
不用你管
Leave me alone.
我只想说
I just mean…
抱歉 就这样
I'm sorry, that's all.
你
You?
你感到抱歉
You're sorry?
不用你可怜 你个丑陋的肥婆
Don't you feel sorry for me, you fat, ugly pig.
你觉得我很丑
You think I'm ugly?
昨天的事我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry about yesterday.
那不是我的本意 知道吗
I didn't mean it, okay?
我一点也不丑
I'm not ugly.
你才丑呢
You're ugly.
我不想再谈论这个了
I'm not talking about it anymore.
我已经将经过都告诉警察和医生了
I already told the cops and the doctors.
根本就没人相信我
No one believes me.
他们都觉得我疯了
They think I'm crazy.
没关系 我的接受能力比大部分人强
Well, I'm a little bit more open-minded than most.
爱普丽尔 为什么跟警察说你被恶魔附身了呢
April, why did you tell the police you were possessed?
那不重要了
It doesn't matter.
它对我来说很重要
It matters to me.
当我
When I …
当我攻击泰勒的时候 我就在那儿 意识清晰
When I hurt Taylor, I was there, in my head,
但却完全无法自控
But I couldn't control my body.
我眼睁睁地看着自己干得一切 就是没法阻止
I could see what I was doing, but I couldn't stop.
我只想停止
I just wanted to stop.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你根本无须道歉
You don't need to apologize.
爱普丽尔 有些同学跟警察说
April, some of the kids at school told the police.
你和泰勒相处的不太好
That you and Taylor didn't get along.
是的 但我从没想过要杀了她
Well, yeah, but I never wanted to kill her.
从没
Never.
你相信我吗
Do you believe me?
当然 我相信
Yeah, I do.
还有几个问题
Just a couple more questions.
事发当天 你有没有
On the day this happened, did you…
闻到什么
Happen to smell anything?
闻到
Anything…
比如什么
Like what?
比如臭鸡蛋或是硫磺的味道
Like rotten eggs or… sulfur?
没有
Um, no.
好吧
Okay.
那你有看到过黑烟吗
Um, did you notice any… black smoke?
你疯了吗
What are you, crazy?
怎样
So?
我认为她说的都是真话
I think she's telling the truth.
从她说的来看更多的是精神层面
I mean, the way she talked about being there mentally.
而不是肉体上的
But not physically …
诸多描述听起来和附身在我体内的恶魔很像
Kind of sounds like demonic possession to me.
诸多
Kind of?
她没有见到任何黑烟或是闻到硫磺味
She didn't see any black smoke or smell sulfur.
也许根本就不是恶魔 有些孩子本身就很邪恶
Maybe it's not a demon. I mean, kids can be vicious.
反正我们都在这儿了
Well, I mean, we're already here.
不如就顺便去学校转悠看看
Might as well check out the school.
对啊 学校
Right. the school.
咋啦
What?
杜鲁门高中 大麻的摇篮
Truman high, home of the bombers.
你想说啥呢
What's your point?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我们之前来这儿 就像
I mean, we went there, like…
是一百万年之前的事了
For a month a million years ago.
- 回这儿为啥你这么兴奋呢 - 我没有
- Why are you so jazzed to go back? - I'm not.
只是觉得值得一查
I just think it's worth looking into.
好吧 我们这次要扮什么呢
All right, well, what's our cover?
联邦调查局还是国土安全局
FBI? homeland security?
要不瑞士交换生如何
Swedish exchange students?
别担心
Don't worry.
我早有主意啦
I got an idea.
好吧
Okay.
谢啦 老爸
Thanks, dad.
午饭带上了吗
got your lunch?
课本 还有折叠刀呢
Books? butterfly knife?
都带了 迪恩
Yeah, Dean.
- 你没事吧 - 当然
- You okay? - sure.
萨姆
Sammy…
说真的
I mean, look,
这已经是我们今年的第三个学校了
This is the third school we've been to this year,
现在才刚十一月
And it's only november.
我不想再当新生了
I'm just sick of always being the new kid.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
要是有人找你麻烦 告诉我
If anyone gives you any trouble, you let me know.
别担心 爸爸说过这次猎鬼最多两个礼拜
Relax. dad said this hunt will take him two weeks, tops.
只要他一回来我们就走人
As soon as he gets back, we're out of here.
再换个学校
To another school.
太棒了
Awesome.
女士们 先生们
ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎 萨姆·温彻斯特
Please say hello to sam winchester.
你好 萨姆
Hi, sam.
同学们 欢迎我们的新同学 迪恩·温彻斯特
Class, say hello to our new student, dean winchester.
迪恩 能跟大家介绍下你自己吗
Dean, Is there anything you'd like to tell us about yourself?
没有 甜心
Not really, sweetheart.
去坐下吧
Take your seat.
能跟大伙介绍下自己吗
Is there anything you'd like to tell us about yourself?
没有
Not really.
好吧 找个位子坐下
Okay. uh, grab a seat.
那是你的吗
Whoa, that's yours?
帅呆了
Awesome!
迪恩 你的书呢
Dean, where are your books?
不需要 甜心
Don't need 'em, sugar.
我在这儿呆不了多久
Not gonna be here long enough anyway.
好了 同学们
All right, gang…
写作作业
Essay assignment.
是啊 是啊 为你们感到难过
Yeah, yeah, my heart breaks for you.
我叫巴里
I'm barry.
萨姆
Sam.
这次要写的是你们最难忘的家庭生活
Okay, now, I want three pages.
要求写满三张纸
Of your most memorable family experience.
别欺负他
leave him alone.
嘘 我正破记录呢
Shh, I'm going for a record.
我说了 别欺负他
I said, "leave him alone."
那欺负你怎么样 小矮子
you want to take his place…midget?
好啊 放马过来
Yeah. sure.
好了 还有什么问题吗
O.K. Anybody for any qusetions?
那开始吧 祝好运
All right, let's get started. good luck.
今天 你们将有幸
today, you will have the honor.
参加有史以来最伟大的游戏
Of playing one of the greatest games ever invented.
一个需要技巧 敏捷和智慧的游戏
A game of skill, agility, cunning.
一个只有一条简单规则的游戏
A game with one simple rule…
躲避球
…dodge.
抱歉
Sorry.
罗斯代教
Uh, substitute coach Roth…
什么事
Yes?
布乔女士从没让我们玩过躲避球
Ms. boudreaux never let us play dodge ball.
布女士正在马萨诸塞州结婚
Well, ms. b's in massachusetts getting married,
所以我们现在来玩
So we're playing.
她说这不安全
She says it's dangerous.
去跑一圈
Take a lap!
可是
But …
开始疯吧
Go nuts.
玩的开心吗
Having fun?
我可以用哨子掌控他们
The whistle makes me their god.
是啊 短裤不错
Right. nice shorts.
找到什么了
Find anything?
我把整所学校彻底搜查了两遍
I've been over the entire school twice.
没有硫磺
No sulfur.
没硫磺就没恶魔 没恶魔就没案件
No sulfur, no demon. no demon, no case.
不知道 可能我搞错了
I don't know. maybe I was wrong.
好吧 看来是这样
Well, it happens to the best of us.
那我们就上路吧
I say we hit the road, huh?
但要等吃完午饭 今天有乔邋遢（一种只有一半的汉堡包）
But after lunch. it's sloppy-joe day.
干的漂亮 科比 得分了
Good hustle, colby! walk it off!
再借我抄一下你的代数作业
Hey, I need to copy your algebra homework again.
为什么
Why?
因为你是个愚蠢的脑残混蛋
'cause you're a stupid, brain-dead dick?
我要用我的拳头捏断你的喉咙 小怪胎
I'm gonna shove my fist down your throat, you little freak.
- 那只拳头吗 - 对
- That fist? - yeah.
怎么回事
What happened?
非暴力集会进行的怎样了
How's the nonviolence assembly going?
显然把孩子的胳膊塞进搅拌机里
Apparently, shoving a kid's arm into a cuisinart.
并非健康的怒气发泄方式
Is not a "healthy display of anger"
有流质流出那孩子的耳朵
So, the kid had ectoplasm leaking out his ear?
只是一个气疯了的鬼魂干的
Which only comes from a seriously pissed-off spirit.
肯定是鬼魂附体
It's got to be ghost possession.
是啊 但那样还真少见
Yeah, but that's pretty rare.
没错 但却发生了
Yeah, but it happens.
到他们足够愤怒的时候
I mean, they get angry enough,
就能操纵人的身体
They can take control of a person's body.
那么 我们是要对付这栋房子里的鬼魂了
All right, so, what, we got a ghost in the building?
对 但是它在哪 探测器找不出来
Yeah, but where? I mean, there's no emf.
也许至少我们能知道它是谁
Maybe we could find out who it is, at least.
查一下惨死在这里之类的案子
You know, check and see if somebody died bloody around here or something.
已经查了
Way ahead of you.
我闯进校长办公室 找到了这个
I had to break into the principal's office to get this.
还有仅供参考
Oh, and fyi,
有三个啦啦队员是合法的
Three of the cheerleaders are legal.
猜是哪三个
Guess which ones.
不
No.
校园里只死过一个人
So, there was only one death on campus.
于98年自杀而亡
It was a suicide back in '98.
他叫巴里·库克
Some kid named barry cook.
怎么
What?
我认识他
I knew him.
他怎么死的
How did he die?
在一楼的女厕所里割腕自尽了
He slit his wrists in the first-floor girls' bathroom.
那里是
That's where …
正是女孩被马桶溺死的地方
Right where the chick got swirleyed to death. exactly.
怎么 这只鬼专挑小人物下手
So, what? this ghost is possessing nerds?
然后利用他们报复欺负他们的人
And using them to go after bullies, yeah.
这像是巴里的订单么
Well, does that sound like barry's m.o.?
巴里有过一段艰难时期
Barry had a hard time.
- 谢谢 萨姆 - 真是好学校
- Thanks, sam. - great school.
我不在乎
I don't care.
三年后 我就解脱了
Three years, and I'm out of here.
我要去密歇根
I'm going to michigan state.
那有全国最好的兽医学校
They got the best vet program in the country.
你喜欢动物吗
Do you like animals?
它们比人好多了
They're a lot nicer than people.
今晚 你和我
So tonight I'm thinking you, me,
还有一桶奶油口味的爆米花
A bucket of popcorn, extra butter…
真有情调
Mm, kinky.
在放映厅看“我唾弃你的坟墓”
And the midnight screening.
感受你的午夜尖叫
Of "I spit on your grave" at the cinedome.
我去不了
I can't.
十一点前要回家
I have a curfew… at 11:00.
那又怎样？
So?
如果我晚回 家人会禁足我一个月
So if I break it, my folks will ground me for a month.
嗯 家长 真恐怖
Yeah, parents. terrifying.
你的宵禁是几点
Well, when's your curfew?
我没有
I don't have one.
难道你爸妈允许你整晚都呆在外面
Your parents just let you stay out all night, don't they?
我爸爸出差了
My dad's out of town on a job.
只剩我和我弟弟
It's just me and my brother.
多久
For how long?
几周
Couple of weeks.
真的
Seriously?
嗯 我们在松树林里有个不错的窝
Yeah, we got a pretty sweet setup at the pines.
汽车旅馆吗
The motel?
卫星电视 免费饮料 棒极了
Hbo, magic fingers, free ice … it's great.
是啊 我也这么觉得
Yeah…i guess.
怎么了？我可以随心所欲
What? I do whatever I want, whenever I want.
多棒啊
It's perfect.
对 但
Yeah, but…
你不想你爸爸吗
Don't you miss your dad?
萨姆
Yo! sammy!
那不是你哥和阿曼达·海克琳吗
That's your brother with amanda heckerling?
他真酷
He's cool.
是啊 他也是这么觉得
Yeah. he thinks so.
嘿 小子
hey, tough guy.
我正找你呢
I been looking for you.
还想代替巴里吗
Still want to take barry's place?
- 离开这 巴里 - 我去找老师
- Get out of here, barry. - I'll go get a teacher.
想走
You want to go?
我不想和你打架 德克
I'm not gonna fight you, dirk.
为什么不 你害怕了吗
Why not? you chicken?
来呀
Come on!
不
No.
站起来 站起来
Get up! get up!
- 来呀 站起来 - 退后
- Come on! get up! - hey, get back!
退后
Get back.
够了
That is enough.
拜拜了 巴里·库克
So long, barry cook.
你没事吧
You all right?
巴里曾是我的朋友
Barry was my friend.
我刚刚烧了他的骨头
I just burned his bones.
他现在安息了 萨姆
Well, he's at peace now, sam.
如果爸爸让我们多呆一段时间
I mean, if dad had let us stay just a little while longer,
也许我就能帮那个孩子了
Maybe I could have helped the kid, you know?
你也看过验尸官的报告了
You read the coroner's report same as me.
巴里吃过目前所有的抗焦虑药
Barry was on every anxiety drug.
还有抗抑郁药
And antidepressant known to man.
学校对那个孩子来说就是地狱
School was hell for that kid.
他的父母离异了 他只想离开
His parents had split up. he just wanted out.
是很悲惨 但这不是你的错
It was tragic, but it's not your fault.
实话告诉你
To tell you the truth,
我很高兴我们离开了那个地方
I'm glad we got out of that town.
我恨那所学校
I hated that school.
也没那么糟
It wasn't all bad.
你遇到了那样的事 怎么还这样说
How can you say that after what happened to you?
- 那家伙死定了 - 迪恩
- That kid's dead. - dean.
我要把他的心挖出来
I'm gonna rip his lungs out!
- 没什么大不了 - 没什么大不了？
- It's not a big deal. - not a big deal?
萨姆 看看你自己 如果爸爸在这
Sammy, look at yourself. if dad was here …
他不在
He's not.
我在
Well, I am!
我一了结那家伙…
And as soon as I'm finished with that dick …
闭嘴 行吗
Shut up, okay?!
不用你帮忙
I don't need your help.
对 你可以自己把他大卸八块
That's right, you don't. you could have torn him apart.
那你为什么不那么做呢
So why didn't you?
因为我这次不想做怪物 迪恩
Because I don't want to be the freak for once, dean.
我想做正常人
I want to be normal.
挨打就算正常了吗
So taking a beating … that's normal?
爸爸那有消息吗
Any word from dad?
他今早打电话来
He called this morning,
说至少还要一周
Said he's going to be another week at least.
我们本不该在这呆这么长时间
We weren't supposed to be here this long.
至少你还有阿曼达
At least you've got amanda.
她还不错
She's cool.
老弟 她想让我见她父母
Dude, she wants me to meet her parents.
我不见父母
I don't do parents.
温彻斯特先生 能和你聊几句吗
Mr. winchester, can I talk to you?
我在外面等你
I'll wait for you outside.
如果是关于打架 不是我开的头
Look, if this is about the fight, I didn't start it.
不 不是关于打架 萨姆
Oh, no, it's not about the fight, sam.
你知道这个作业不是写小说 是吧
You know this assignment was nonfiction, right?
是的 怀特先生
Yes, mr. wyatt.
那你和你家人去年夏天杀了个狼人吗
So you and your family killed a werewolf last summer, huh?
你为什么要写这样的东西 萨姆
Why would you write something like this, sam?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
我爸爸一回来我们就走
As soon as my dad gets back, we're leaving.
所以如果你想 可以让我不及格
So you can flunk me if you want to.
我不会给你不及格 我给你优秀
I'm not flunking you. I'm giving you an "a."
先不说那个狼人
Now, aside from the werewolf,
你真是那样想你家人的？
Is that really how you'd describe your family?
是的
Yeah.
你哥真是个人物
Well, your brother is quite a character.
还有你爸爸 看起来也是被逼的
And your father … he seems, uh, driven.
不管怎样 这很好 萨姆 真的很好
Anyway, it's good, sam. it's really good.
想过从事写作吗
Have you ever thought about pursuing writing?
我不能
I can't.
我得从事家族事业
I have to go into the family business.
家族事业？
Family business?
对 我爸爸是个…
Yeah, my dad's a m…
我爸爸是个机械工
My dad's a mechanic.
所以我也必须做机械工
So I have to be a mechanic, too.
你想从事家族事业吗
Do you want to go in the family business, sam?
之前没人这么问过我
No one's ever asked me that before.
你想吗
Well?
不
More than anything, no.
我不想过界 但是
I don't want to overstep my bounds here, but…
你不必做你不想做的事
…you don't have to do anything you don't want to do.
我知道那是什么感觉
Look, I mean, I know what it's like.
我们家是个医生世家 但我不想
I come from a family of surgeons, and that wasn't me.
所以 你看
So, you know, I traded in.
我用钱和医生的声望
The money and prestige of being a doctor.
换来现在你所看到的一切
For all the glamour you see around you.
重要的是…
But the point is…
也许 有几个重大抉择
There may be three or four big choices.
会决定一个人的一生
That shape someone's whole life,
而你需要成为那个作出决定的人
And you need to be the one that makes them,
不是其他人
Not anyone else.
你看上去是个很好的孩子
You seem like a great kid, Sam.
过你想过的生活吧
Just live the life you want to live.
我们回到这就是为了让你和老师谈心？
We came back here so you could talk to a teacher?
他是个好人
He's a good guy.
无所谓
Well, whatever.
找你的授业恩师去吧
Go have your Robin Williams.
「哦 冠军 我的冠军」
"o captain! my captain!" moment.
动作快点
Just make it quick.
打扰了 先生
Excuse me, Sir.
能告诉我305室怎么走吗
Can you tell me how to find room 305?
当然
Sure. um…
大厅尽头 第一个拐角右转
Head down the hall, take your first right,
左手边第三个门
And it's the third door on the left.
谢谢 萨姆
Thanks, sam.
你长高了 温切斯特先生
You got tall, Winchester.
相信我 这会有用的
Trust me. This will help.
那个鬼死定了 我要把它的心挖出来
That ghost is dead. I'm gonna rip its lungs out!
你知道我的意思
Well, you know what I mean.
它知道我的名字 迪恩
It knew my name, Dean.
我的真名
My real name.
我们烧了巴里的尸骨
We burned Barry's bones.
到底是怎么回事
What the hell?
也许不是巴里 也许我们忽略了什么
Well, maybe it wasn't Barry. Maybe we missed something.
我们回头想想
We just got to go back.
不会吧
No way.
我们之前怎么没发现
How did we not see this before?
- 什么 - 看看
- What? - Check it out.
看 Martha Dumptruck
Look, Martha Dumptruck,
蠢货的报复 还有hello kitty
Revenge of the nerds, and hello kitty …
他们乘坐同一辆巴士
They all rode the same bus.
好吧 也许那巴士闹鬼
Okay, so maybe the bus is haunted.
那就能解释为什么学校里没有电磁干扰
Well, that would explain why there's no emf at the school,
但解释不了袭击事件
But not the attacks.
鬼魂应该被束缚在他们死的地方
I mean, ghosts are tied to the places that they haunt.
他们不能随便跑出来
They can't just bail.
除非这个鬼能
Unless this one can.
迪恩 有些关于鬼附身的传说
Dean, there's lore about spirits possessing people.
他们可以支配人四下走动
And riding them for miles.
当他们离开宿主的时候
Then whenever they leave the body,
他们就会回到自己的地盘
They're bungeed back to their usual haunt.
但离开宿主之前 他们想去哪就去哪
But until then, the ghosts can go wherever they want.
那鬼魂附在巴士上一个孩子身上
So a spook just grabs a kid on the bus.
然后大摇大摆走进杜鲁门高中？
And walks right into Truman?
有可能
It's possible.
恶鬼也有创意 真是绝了
Ghosts getting creative … well, that's super.
显然是个是非之地
Definitely ain't clean.
到这来 小鬼头…
Here, ghosty, ghosty, ghosty!
出来吧 出来吧 不管你在哪里
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
哥们 我不明白
Man, I don't get it.
从没人死在这辆巴士上
No one ever died on this bus,
而且也没什么尸骨藏在这里
And it's not like there's a body hidden in here.
嗯 但皮肤 头发 肉刺什么的
Yeah, but a flap of skin, a hair, I mean, hell, a hangnail,
一定有什么东西把鬼束缚在这里
Something's got to be tying the ghost to this place.
我们得找到那东西
We just got to find it.
嗯
Yeah.
找到个新的驾驶执照
Got a new driving permit.
两周前发的
Issued two weeks ago.
就在第一次袭击之前
Just before the first attack.
嗯
Yeah.
巴士司机的名字叫老德克 Mcgregor
Name of the bus driver is Dirk Mcgregor Sr.
北中央大街39号
39 north central avenue.
- Mcgregor？-嗯
Mcgregor? Yeah.
怎么啦
Why?
我认识他儿子
I knew his son.
你是不是认识这学校的每个人
Did you know everybody at this school?
看着路 小子
Got to watch where you're going, man.
别惹他 德克
Leave him alone, Dirk.
你就不长记性是吧 小矮人
You never learn, do you, midget?
上车 巴里
Get to the bus, Barry.
怎么 你害怕了？
What's the matter? You scared?
别担心
Don't worry.
这次我会对你手下留情
I'll go easy on you this time.
来 废人切斯特 看看你有什么本事
Come on, lose-chester. Let's see what you got.
来吧 怪胎
Come on, freak!
怪胎
Freak!
你也没那么强
You're not tough.
你只是个混蛋
You're just a jerk.
德克大混蛋
"Dirk the jerk."
"Dirk the jerk!"
你和德克是朋友？
So, you were friends with Dirk?
是的 先生 高中时
Yes, sir, in high school.
我不记得德克在高中有那么多朋友
I don't recall Dirk having many friends at Truman.
请坐 请坐
Here, sit. sit down.
什么时候…德克什么时候过世的
When did, uh … when did Dirk pass?
他18岁的时候
He was 18.
出了什么事
What happened to him?
第一 酗酒
Well, there was, first, drinking,
再就是嗑药 太多的药
Then drugs, and then too many drugs.
然后他就从我生命里消失了
And then he just slipped through my fingers.
都是我的错
It was my fault.
我该预见到这点
I should have seen it coming, you know?
德克 他…他有他的烦恼
Dirk, he, uh … well, he had his troubles.
什么样的烦恼
What kind of troubles?
上学对德克是件难事
School was never easy for Dirk.
我们并没有多少钱
We didn't have much money,
你知道 孩子 也可以是很残忍的
And, well, you know, kids … they can be cruel.
他们总找他的麻烦
They picked on him.
他们找他的麻烦？
They picked on him?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
他们说他又穷又脏又蠢
They called him poor and dirty and stupid.
他们还给他起了外号
They even had a nickname for him …
德克大混蛋
Dirk the jerk.
在他母亲出事之后 他就…
And after what happened to his mother, he …
他母亲？
His mother?
嗯 简 我的妻子
Yeah, Jane, my wife.
德克13岁的时候她过世了
She died when Dirk was 13.
癌症
Cancer.
我忙于三份工作
I was working three jobs,
所以把照顾她的责任全留给了德克
So it fell to Dirk to take care of her.
他是个好孩子
And he was a great kid.
他保证简得到治疗
He made sure Jane got her medicine.
他帮她 为她善后
He helped her, cleaned up after her.
但是 当你看着一个人慢慢死去
But, you know, you … you watch somebody die slow,
日渐消瘦…
Waste away to nothing…
这会对人有影响
It does things to a person.
可怕的影响
Horrible things.
我不知道他妈妈的事
I didn't know about his mother.
他从不谈她
He … he wouldn't talk about her,
对我也不谈
Not even to me.
他心里积压了太多的怨气
Lot of anger in that boy.
我很难过
I'm sorry.
麦格雷戈先生 我们想凭吊一下
Well, we'd really like to pay our respects, Mr.Mcgregor.
能告诉我们德克葬在哪吗
Um, you mind telling us where dirk is buried?
他不是土葬的 我把他火化了
Oh, he wasn't. I had him cremated.
整个身体吗
All of him?
我保存了他的一绺头发
Well, I kept a lock of his hair.
那 那挺好
Oh, that's … that's nice.
放在哪了
Where do you keep that?
我的车上 夹在圣经里
On my bus, in my bible.
谢谢你今晚替班 艾迪
Thanks for subbing tonight, eddie.
我的荣幸 教练
My pleasure, coach.
艾迪 开慢点行吗
Eddie, you want to ease up on the pedal, there?
我开得稳着呢
I got it all under control.
怎么回事
What the hell was that?
大家没事吧
Everyone okay?
德克
Dirk!
温彻斯特
Winchester.
你想怎样 向我开枪吗
What are you gonna do, shoot me?
没这个必要
Don't need to.
绳子浸过盐水 德克
That rope is soaked in salt water, dirk.
你哪也别想去
You're not going anywhere.
所有人都呆在原地 你们会没事的
All right, everybody stay where you are. you'll be okay.
你不是体育老师吗
Aren't you the p.e. teacher?
不是 我就像“少年龙虎队”
Not really. I'm like "21 jump street."
司机贩毒
The bus driver sells pot.
就是这样
Yeah.
不在这
It's not here!
头发在哪
Where is it?
你永远找不到
No way you'll ever find it.
在哪
Where is it?!
萨姆·温彻斯特
Sam winchester.
还是个恶霸
Still a bully.
你 你们这些运动员
You, you jocks…
你们这些受欢迎的孩子
You popular kids…
你们总认为自己高人一等
You always thought you were better than everybody else.
在你们眼里 我只是德克蠢蛋
And to you, I was just dirk the jerk, right?
现在一报还一报
Now you evil sons of bitches are gonna get what's coming to you.
我不是恶魔 德克
I'm not evil, dirk.
我不是
I'm not.
你也不是
And neither were you.
相信我 我见过真正的恶魔
Trust me. I've seen real evil.
我们只是害怕而且痛苦
We were scared and miserable,
然后跟彼此 跟所有人都过不去
And we took it out on each other …
来转移这种情绪
Us and everybody else.
那是高中
That's high school.
但这些都过去了 现在好了
But you suffer through that, and it gets better.
很遗憾你无法看到
I'm just sorry you didn't get a chance to see that…
你和巴里
You or barry.
没什么能让我感到一丝好受
Nothing is gonna get better for me.
从来都没有
Not ever.
迪恩 找头发
Dean! find the hair!
伙计 事情并非看上去那样
Hey, buddy, this isn't what it looks like.
帮帮忙
Little help?
他给你一个大满怀
He's giving you the full cowgirl.
再等5分钟 杰里
Five more minutes, jerry.
阿曼达
Amanda, hey!
盖茨堡演说 1863年 是吧
Gettysburg address, 1863, right?
下节课历史测验 我们正在学习
History test next period. we're studying.
别这样宝贝 她对我什么都不是
Come on, baby. she means nothing to me.
别生气
Don't be mad.
我没生气 迪恩
I'm not mad, dean.
我以为 或许
I thought maybe…
你的鬼扯 你的调皮
Underneath your whole "i could give a crap, " bad-boy thing,
只是你的表面
That there was something more going on.
就像你和你兄弟在一起时那样
I mean, like the way you are with your brother.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
你费尽心思
And you spend so much time.
让别人相信你很酷
Trying to convince people that you're cool,
只是作秀
But it's just an act.
你不过是个悲伤
We both know that you're just a sad…
孤独的孩子而已
Lonely little kid.
我为你感到难过 迪恩
And I feel sorry for you, dean.
你为我感到难过？
You feel sorry for me, huh?
别为我感到难过
Don't feel sorry for me.
你对我一无所知
You don't know anything about me.
我拯救生命
I save lives.
我是英雄 英雄
I'm a hero. a hero!
怎么
What?
What?!
老爸
Dad?
终于
Finally.
我真等不及离开这鬼地方
I can't wait to get the hell out of here.
这地方太烂了
This place sucks.
快来 萨姆
Come on, sam.
怀特先生
Uh, mr. wyatt?
我是
Yes.
你可能不记得我了
You probably don't remember me,
我叫萨姆·温彻斯特
Um, but my name is sam winchester,
我想来谢谢你
And I just wanted to thank you.
谢什么
For?
我以前是这的学生
I was a student here,
你给过我一些建议
And you gave me some advice once.
温彻斯特 对 对
Winchester, right. right. yeah.
你 你写了那个恐怖故事
You, uh … you wrote that horror story.
对 我写过
Yeah. yeah, I did.
一直是个长篇恐怖故事
Yeah, it's kind of all been one long horror story.
什么意思
What do you mean?
没什么 抱歉
Nothing. sorry.
是什么建议？
So, what was this advice?
我以后可能需要剽窃一下自己
I might need to plagiarize myself down the line.
你跟我说 我不必加入家族事业
You told me that I didn't have to go into the family business.
你说我应该遵从自己的意愿
You said I should make my own choices.
之后你开始做自己喜爱的事了？
Oh. so you've managed to do your own thing, then, huh?
对 做了段时间
Yeah, for a while, yeah.
因为你 我去念了大学
And I think I went to college because of you.
但 人总会长大
But, you know, people grow up.
对
Yeah.
责任
Responsibilities.
但
But still, um…
从来没人像你这么关心过我
You took an interest in me when no one else did.
这很重要 谢谢你
That matters, so thanks you.
唯一重要的是
Well, you know, the only thing that really matters.
你感到开心
Is that you're happy.
你开心吗 萨姆
Are you happy, sam?